[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0502_0101_ancientscholar",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0502_0101_d_00_container_ancientscholar",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0502_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0502_0101_ancientscholar_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0502_0101_ancientscholar_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0502_0101_ancientscholar_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0502_0101_ancientscholar_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0502_0101_ancientscholar_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0502_0101_ancientscholar_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0502_0101_ancientscholar_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0502_0102_hopespringseternal",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0502_0102_d_00_container_hopespringseternal",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0502_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0502_0102_hopespringseternal_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0502_0102_hopespringseternal_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0502_0102_hopespringseternal_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0502_0102_hopespringseternal_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0502_0102_hopespringseternal_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0502_0102_hopespringseternal_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0502_0102_hopespringseternal_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0502_0103_pathsunseen",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0502_0103_d_00_container_pathsunseen",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0502_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0502_0103_pathsunseen_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0502_0103_pathsunseen_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0502_0103_pathsunseen_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0502_0103_pathsunseen_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0502_0103_pathsunseen_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0502_0103_pathsunseen_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0502_0103_pathsunseen_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0502_0104_anatomyoftheheart",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0502_0104_d_00_container_anatomyoftheheart",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0502_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0502_0104_anatomyoftheheart_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0502_0104_anatomyoftheheart_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0502_0104_anatomyoftheheart_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0502_0104_anatomyoftheheart_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0502_0104_anatomyoftheheart_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0502_0104_anatomyoftheheart_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0502_0104_anatomyoftheheart_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0502_0105_seekandhide",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0502_0105_d_00_container_seekandhide",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0511_Stranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0502_0105_seekandhide_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0502_0105_seekandhide_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0502_0105_seekandhide_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0502_0105_seekandhide_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0502_0105_seekandhide_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0502_0105_seekandhide_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0502_0105_seekandhide_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0511_0101_aguardiansplight",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0511_0101_d_00_container_aguardiansplight",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0502_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0511_0101_aguardiansplight_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "0511_0101_aguardiansplight_failure",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0511_0101_aguardiansplight_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0511_0101_aguardiansplight_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0511_0101_aguardiansplight_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0511_0101_aguardiansplight_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0511_0101_aguardiansplight_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0511_0101_aguardiansplight_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0504_0101_anexpandingthreat",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0504_0101_d_00_container_anexpandingthreat",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0504_0101_anexpandingthreat_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "0504_0102_defianceanddoubt",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0504_0101_anexpandingthreat_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0504_0101_anexpandingthreat_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0504_0101_anexpandingthreat_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0504_0101_anexpandingthreat_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0504_0101_anexpandingthreat_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0504_0101_anexpandingthreat_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0504_0102_defianceanddoubt",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0504_0102_d_00_container_defianceanddoubt",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0524_Stranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0504_0102_defianceanddoubt_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0504_0102_defianceanddoubt_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0504_0102_defianceanddoubt_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0504_0102_defianceanddoubt_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0504_0102_defianceanddoubt_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0504_0102_defianceanddoubt_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0524_0101_ahungerforfreedom",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0524_0101_d_00_container_ahungerforfreedom",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0524_Stranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0524_0101_ahungerforfreedom_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0524_0101_ahungerforfreedom_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0524_0101_ahungerforfreedom_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0524_0101_ahungerforfreedom_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0524_0101_ahungerforfreedom_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0524_0101_ahungerforfreedom_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0524_0101_ahungerforfreedom_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0524_0102_queensgambit",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0524_0102_d_00_container_queensgambit",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0524_Stranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_09",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0524_0102_queensgambit_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0524_0102_queensgambit_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0524_0102_queensgambit_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0524_0102_queensgambit_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0524_0102_queensgambit_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0524_0102_queensgambit_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0524_0102_queensgambit_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0524_0103_shiveringtimbers",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0524_0103_d_00_container_shiveringtimbers",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0504_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_10",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0524_0103_shiveringtimbers_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0524_0103_shiveringtimbers_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0524_0103_shiveringtimbers_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0524_0103_shiveringtimbers_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0524_0103_shiveringtimbers_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0524_0103_shiveringtimbers_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0524_0103_shiveringtimbers_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0504_0201_wordsofpower",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0504_0201_d_00_container_wordsofpower",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0504_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0504_0201_wordsofpower_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0504_0201_wordsofpower_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0504_0201_wordsofpower_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0504_0201_wordsofpower_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0504_0201_wordsofpower_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0504_0201_wordsofpower_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0504_0201_wordsofpower_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0504_0202_aplansdeconstruction",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0504_0202_d_00_container_aplansdeconstruction",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0504_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_13",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_12",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0504_0202_aplansdeconstruction_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0504_0202_aplansdeconstruction_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0504_0202_aplansdeconstruction_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0504_0202_aplansdeconstruction_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0504_0202_aplansdeconstruction_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0504_0202_aplansdeconstruction_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0504_0202_aplansdeconstruction_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0504_0401_thequeenisdead",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0504_0401_d_00_container_thequeenisdead",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0504_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_22",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_13",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0504_0401_thequeenisdead_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0504_0401_thequeenisdead_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0504_0401_thequeenisdead_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0504_0401_thequeenisdead_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0504_0401_thequeenisdead_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0504_0401_thequeenisdead_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0504_0401_thequeenisdead_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0510_0101_longlivethequeen",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0510_0101_d_00_container_longlivethequeen",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_22",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0510_0101_longlivethequeen_success",
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0510_0101_longlivethequeen_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0510_0101_longlivethequeen_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0510_0101_longlivethequeen_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0510_0101_longlivethequeen_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0510_0101_longlivethequeen_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0510_0101_longlivethequeen_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0503_0101_onfloralfauna",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0503_0101_d_00_container_onfloralfauna",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0503_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_14",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0503_0101_onfloralfauna_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0503_0101_onfloralfauna_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0503_0101_onfloralfauna_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0503_0101_onfloralfauna_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0503_0101_onfloralfauna_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0503_0101_onfloralfauna_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0503_0101_onfloralfauna_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0505_0101_pruningandirrigation",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0505_0101_d_00_container_pruningandirrigation",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0505_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_15",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_14",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0505_0101_pruningandirrigation_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0505_0101_pruningandirrigation_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0505_0101_pruningandirrigation_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0505_0101_pruningandirrigation_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0505_0101_pruningandirrigation_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0505_0101_pruningandirrigation_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0505_0101_pruningandirrigation_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0505_0102_downstreameffects",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0505_0102_d_00_container_downstreameffects",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0505_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_16",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_15",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0505_0102_downstreameffects_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0505_0102_downstreameffects_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0505_0102_downstreameffects_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0505_0102_downstreameffects_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0505_0102_downstreameffects_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0505_0102_downstreameffects_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0505_0102_downstreameffects_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0503_0201_excisingtheblightedroot",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0503_0201_d_00_container_excisingtheblightedroot",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0503_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_16",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0503_0201_excisingtheblightedroot_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0503_0201_excisingtheblightedroot_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0503_0201_excisingtheblightedroot_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0503_0201_excisingtheblightedroot_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0503_0201_excisingtheblightedroot_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0503_0201_excisingtheblightedroot_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0503_0201_excisingtheblightedroot_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0503_0202_burdenofatonement",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0503_0202_d_00_container_burdenofatonement",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0503_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_18",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_17",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0503_0202_burdenofatonement_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0503_0202_burdenofatonement_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0503_0202_burdenofatonement_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0503_0202_burdenofatonement_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0503_0202_burdenofatonement_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0503_0202_burdenofatonement_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0503_0202_burdenofatonement_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0503_0203_wardensofthegreen",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0503_0203_d_00_container_wardensofthegreen",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0503_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_18",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0503_0203_wardensofthegreen_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0503_0203_wardensofthegreen_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0503_0203_wardensofthegreen_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0503_0203_wardensofthegreen_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0503_0203_wardensofthegreen_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0503_0203_wardensofthegreen_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0503_0203_wardensofthegreen_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0503_0301_theeternalpool",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0503_0301_d_00_container_theeternalpool",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0503_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_20",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_19",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0503_0301_theeternalpool_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0503_0301_theeternalpool_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0503_0301_theeternalpool_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0503_0301_theeternalpool_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0503_0301_theeternalpool_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0503_0301_theeternalpool_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0503_0301_theeternalpool_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "ReekwaterArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0505_0103_thedryadpromenade",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0505_0103_d_00_container_thedryadpromenade",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_20",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0505_0103_thedryadpromenade_success",
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0505_0103_thedryadpromenade_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0505_0103_thedryadpromenade_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0505_0103_thedryadpromenade_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0505_0103_thedryadpromenade_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0505_0103_thedryadpromenade_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0505_0103_thedryadpromenade_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0502_0106_primevalcyclops",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0502_0106_d_00_container_primevalcyclops",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0502_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "05_Quest_Lazarus_21",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "05_Quest_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0502_0106_primevalcyclops_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0502_0106_primevalcyclops_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0502_0106_primevalcyclops_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0502_0106_primevalcyclops_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0502_0106_primevalcyclops_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0502_0106_primevalcyclops_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0502_0106_primevalcyclops_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_05_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_05_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_05_PVP_PoachArea_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_05_PVP_PoachArea_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_05_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_05_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_05_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_05_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_05_PVP_PoachArea_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_05_PVP_PoachArea_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_05_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_05_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_05_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_05_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_05_PVP_PoachArea_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_05_PVP_PoachArea_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_05_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_05_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0501_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0501_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0502_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0502_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0503_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0503_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0504_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0504_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0505_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0505_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0506_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0506_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0507_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0507_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0501_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0501_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0502_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0502_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0503_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0503_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0504_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0504_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0505_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0505_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0506_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0506_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0507_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0507_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0501_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0501_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0502_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0502_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0503_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0503_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0504_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0504_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0505_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0505_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0506_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0506_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0507_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0507_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0561_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0561_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0562_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0562_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0563_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0563_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0564_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0564_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0565_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0565_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0566_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0566_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0567_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0567_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0561_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0561_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0562_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0562_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0563_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0563_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0564_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0564_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0565_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0565_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0566_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0566_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0567_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0567_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0561_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0561_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0562_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0562_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0563_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0563_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0564_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0564_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0565_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0565_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0566_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0566_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0567_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0567_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_05_H_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_05_H_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_05_H_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_05_H_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_05_H_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_05_H_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 5,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_05_EXP_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_05_EXP_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_05_EXP_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_05_EXP_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_05_EXP_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_05_EXP_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    }
]